Guide to the Records of the Institute of African American Affairs RG.9.8
New York University Archives
- Series III: Earl S. Davis Correspondence
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Goines, Dr. Leonard, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Kan, Michael, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Mitchell, Loften, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Young, Joseph, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Young, Philip, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - IAAA Book Fair, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - IAAA Conference Reports, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - IAAA Evaluations, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - IAAA Fact Sheet, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - IAAA Fundraising, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - IAAA Fundraising, Benefit Performance, 1st Anniversary- Steve Depass, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - IAAA Fundraising, Benefit Performance, 1st Anniversary- Steve Depass, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - IAAA Lecture: Alex Haley, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - IAAA Progress Report (1), 1970 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - IAAA Progress Report (2), 1970 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - IAAA Proposal for Research: IAAA Training Minority Group Research and Evaluation Specialists, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226037 5
  - IAAA Publicity, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - IAAA Report, Fall Term, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - IAAA Staff Bulletin, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - IAAA Staff Report, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - IAAA Steering Committee, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Journal of Negro Education, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Center Correspondence, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Center Correspondence, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Center Publications: "The Niggafied Press" Volumes 3-8, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - NYU Publication: Internal for Faculty and Administration, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - The New York Urban Coalition (1), 1970 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - The New York Urban Coalition (2), 1970 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Proposal for Research, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Sojourner Newspaper, Publication of IAAA, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Still Here Magazine, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Washington Square Journal, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Black Articles, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Black Creation, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Black Literary, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Black Studies Courses, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Black Studies Course Listing, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Black Studies Programs in the U.S., 1971 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Black Studies Speakers, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Chancellor's Report, IAAA, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence of E. R. Braithwaite, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence of E. R. Braithwaite, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence of Dr. Roscoe Brown, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Directories-Business, Educational (National Periodicals and Journals), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - IAAA Activities-Program Planning, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee Correspondence, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Coombs, Orde, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Exum, William, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Floyd, Art, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Furman, Roger, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Garriga, Jose, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Grimes, Larry, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Hall, Fred, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Holmes, Robert, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Jenkins, Adelbert, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Jordan, John Samuel, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Mickens, Al, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Ofonogoro, Walter, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Thornton, Virginius, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Walker, Dr. Wyatt T., 1971 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - IAAA Fundraising, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - IAAA Orientation (1), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - IAAA Orientation (2), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - IAAA Staff, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - IMANI Magazine, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - IMANI Magazine, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - The Institute of the Black World Monthly Report, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Center, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Kirng, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Scholarships, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - M.A. Program in Black Studies, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Minority Student Recruitment, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226038 3
  - NYU Publication: Internal for Faculty and Administrators, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Report to Ford Foundation, IAAA, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Exchange Program, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square Journal, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Agbeli, Godwin-African Dance Class, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Art Collection-Grey Art Gallery, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Black Articles, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Black Creation, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Black Creation, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Black Films, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Black Studies Courses, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Black Studies in Higher Education, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Dr. Roscoe Brown, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Directory - Black Urban Alliances, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Final Report to the Ford Foundation, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Giovanni, Nikki, Reception, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - IAAA AEJ Program, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - IAAA History/Research, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - IAAA History/Research, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - IAAA History/Research, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - IAAA Staff, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - IAAA Training Program-Community College Black Studies Instructors, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - IAAA Training Program: Junior or Community College Teachers in Black Studies, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - The Institute of the Black World Monthly Report, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther King Center, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Program, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - M.A. Program in Black Studies, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Mathematical Sciences - List of Departmental Chairpersons, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - NYU Publication: Internal for Faculty & Admin., 1972 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Proposals for Funding of Research Projects, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Research Project: Community College, Black Studies Instructors, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Sojourner Newspaper, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Sojourner Newspaper, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Sports Foundation, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Washington Square Journal, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Wooden's John-Success Project, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - IAAA Fundraising, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - IAAA Newsletter, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Black Creation Magazine, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Black Films, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Black Literary, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Black Studies Courses, Graduate Level, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - BSSC (Black Student Service Center) Proposal, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence: Dr. Roscoe Brown, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Dilemmas of Afro-Americans (IAAA Course) taught by Dr. Eugene Callender, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - IAAA Annual Report (1), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - IAAA Annual Report (2), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - IAAA Annual Report (3), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - IAAA Project: Instructional Strategies and the Development of Political Thinking Among Emerging Adolescents, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - IAAA Project: Instructional Strategies and the Development of Political Thinking Among Emerging Adolescents, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - IAAA Staff Correspondence, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - The Institute of the Black World Monthly Report, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Journalism Council (Job/Scholarship Referral Bulletin For Minorities), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Reception, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Memorial Program, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - NYU Publication: Internal for Faculty and Administrators, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - NYU Staff Publication, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - The New York Urban Coalition, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Association of Black Faculty, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226039 1
  - BSSC (Black Student Service Center), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Black Studies Programs, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - IAAA Annual Report (2), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - IAAA Annual Report (3), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - IAAA Annual Report (4), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - IAAA Annual Report (draft), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - IAAA Mainstream (Radio Production/Show), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - IAAA Newsletter "Notes", 1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - IAAA Program Planning, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - IAAA Proposal for Evaluation of Title I and Title VII Program, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Journalism Council, Inc., 1974 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Fourth Annual Memorial Services, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Reception for Graduates, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Minority Graduate Student Locater Service, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - NYU Report Biweekly/Journal, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Robinson, Jackie Management Corp., 1974 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Walker, Dr. Leroy (NYU Alumnus), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Washington Square News, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Black Creation Magazine Copyrights, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Black Films, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Blacks in Higher Education Articles, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Black Student Service Center, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, Dr. Roscoe Brown, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - IAAA Advisory, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - IAAA Graduate Planning Center Student Information Sheet, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - IAAA Graduate Planning Center Student Information Sheet, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - IAAA Mainstream (WNYU Radio Show), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - IAAA Planning, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - The Institute of the Black World Monthly Report, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Journalism Council, Inc., 1975 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Reception, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Program-Memorial, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - NYU Report Biweekly/Journal, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Proposal Writing Workshop, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Still Here Magazine, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence - W. Barbee, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Art Collection-Grey Art Gallery, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Association of Black Faculty, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Bicentennial Celebration (IAAA at NYU), 1976 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Black Films, William Greaves, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Black Genealogy Book Compilation, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226040 9
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: (2) Baraka, Amiri, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: (3) Booth, Judge W., 1976 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: (4) Coombs, Ode., 1976 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: (5) Higgins, Jr., Chester, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: (6) Tolliver, Melba, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Black Student Service Center, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Ebony Patriots Magazine, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - IAAA Inventory, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - IAAA Program Planning, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - IAAA Summary of the Activities of the Institute of Afro-American Affairs, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - IAAA Seminar - 20th Century Black Radicalism, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - IAAA Staff Correspondence, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Institutional Racism: Implications for Social Workers, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Journalism Articles/Guide-Directory, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther - Graduate Certificates, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther - Graduate Certificates, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther - Graduate Certificates, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther - Graduate Certificates, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther - Graduate Reception, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther - Memorial, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Leadbelly Screening and Chronology, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - The Little Black Book, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - New York University Report Newspaper, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Sports Foundation, Inc., 1976 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Still Here Magazine, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Survey of Undergraduate Black Studies Courses at NYU, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Association of Black Faculty, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Gil Noble, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: John O. Killens, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Basil Peterson, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Franklin Williams, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Mary Lou Williams, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Black Student Service Center, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Black Studies Research: Articles from 1969-1970, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Black Studies Research: Articles from 1973-1977 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - IAAA Annual Report-Proposed Plans/Programs, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - IAAA For Your Information, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduation Reception, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduation Reception, Student Responses, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Memorial, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226041 7
  - Literary Associations, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - National Conference of Artists, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - National Conference of Artists, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - New York University Report Newspaper, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - The New York Urban Coalition, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Police Athletic League, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Schomberg, Arthur A. Award Dinner at the Waldorf Astoria, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Sports Foundation, Inc., 1977 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Woodruff, Hale, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Black Creation Magazine, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - IAAA Graduate Planning Center Student Information Sheet, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - IAAA Newsletter, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - IAAA Newsletter, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Afro-American Cultural Foundation, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Association of Black Faculty, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Black Collegian Magazine, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Lenox Hinds, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Benjamin Hooks, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Dr. Inez Smith Reid, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Ntozake Shange, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: John A. Williams, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Blacks in Higher Education Articles, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Cinque Gallery Board Meetings, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, W. Barbee, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Graduate Student Reception, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - IAAA For Your Information, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - IAAA Graduate Planning Center, Forms/Responses, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - IAAA Inventory, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - IAAA Newsbrief, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - IAAA Program Assistant, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - IAAA Space Inventory, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - IAAA Staff Projects/Activities, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - The Little Black Book Magazine, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Bibliographical Outline, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Bibliographical Outline, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Association (First Annual Awards Dinner), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduation Reception, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Memorial, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Scholarship Fund, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - New York University Report Publication, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - The New York Urban Coalition, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Second International Congress on Education, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence- Dr. Edward M. Carroll, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - ABFA Minority Student Achievement Award Recipients, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226042 5
  - ABFA Minority Student Achievement Award Recipients, Correspondence, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Afro-American Studies Program, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Black History Month Planning, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Black History Month Planning, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Black Literature, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Black Religion, news articles, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Correspondence and General Information, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Dr. John Henrik Clarke, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Dr. Edyth J. Gaines, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Dr. Jeanne Noble, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Gordon Parks, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: James Steele, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Black Studies Programs in the U.S., 1979 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Black Student Service Center, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Cinque Gallery Board Meetings, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Dr. Edward M. Carroll, Acting Director, IAAA, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Earl Davis, Director-IAAA, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Fundraising, IAAA, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Graduate Student Reception, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - IAAA Black Student Organization Steering Committee Meeting, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - IAAA Brochure, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - IAAA Program Planning, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - IAAA Questionnaire - Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Material Packet, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Reception, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther, Memorial Ceremony, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther, Memorial Ceremony, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther, Memorial Ceremony, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Monograph Series, Volume I, Number I, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Renwick Reception, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Research-Enrollment/Black Studies Courses Offered at NYU, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Secretarial Recruitment, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Washington Square News, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - ABFA Constitution, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Afro-American Courses and Related Subjects Listing, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Benin Exhibition Correspondence, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series General Correspondence, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Black Scholars Series Speakers: "Economic Development in the Black Community: 'What Will the 80's Bring?'" by Arthur H. Barnes, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Black Scholars Series Speakers: "The Black Image in the Media" by David Lampel, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Black Scholars Series Speakers: "Metamorphosis-Poetry Reading" Featuring Quincy Troupe, Fred Nelson, Regina Williams, Mariah Britton Howard, Wayne Providence, Cathering Sanders, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Black Scholars Series Speakers: "The 80's - Which Way for Black America," Guest Speaker Congressman Charles B. Rangel, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - BSSC, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - BSSO, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Black Studies Programs Research, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Citicorp/NYU Business Career Forum for Minority Undergraduate Students, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Citicorp/NYU Business Career Forum for Minority Undergraduate Students, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Citicorp/NYU Business Career Forum for Minority Undergraduate Students, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence - Earl Davis, Director, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226043 3
  - Correspondence - Louise Dennis, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "Emerging African Nations," Correspondence - Ambassadors, Conference, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "Emerging African Nations," Forms, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "Emerging African Nations," List of African Ambassadors, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - "Emerging African Nations," Program Operations, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - IAAA Inventory, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - IAAA Lecturer/Speakers, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 10)